Semel, Elisabeth; Collection apap332
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Issues and Topics, 1977-2009; 2; 3 cubic ft.
  This series contains articles covering different issues dealing with the death penalty including costs, public opinion, and race. The largest sections are counsel, mental retardation, and opinions, with articles from the 1990s to the early 2000s. Notably, the opinion section contains articles on international opinion as well as domestic views on the death penalty.
  - Capitalism, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 1)
  - Chicago Tribune Confession Series, December, 2001-2001 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 2)
  - Conditions, 2001; 2003 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 3)
  - Costs (1 of 2), 1991-1995; 1998-2006; 2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 4)
  - Costs (2 of 2), 1991-1995; 1998-2006; 2009; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 5)
  - Counsel - Pre 2000, 1990; 1993; 1996-2000; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 6)
  - Counsel - 1990s-2000s, 1993; 1997-1998; 2002-2004; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 7)
  - Counsel (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 8)
  - Counsel (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 9)
  - Counsel - January-June (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 10)
  - Counsel - January-June (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 11)
  - Counsel - July-December, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 12)
  - Counsel, 2002 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 13)
  - Counsel - 2003, 2002-2004 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 14)
  - Counsel - 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 15)
  - Counsel - 2005-2007, 2006-2007; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 16)
  - Crime - Prevention, 1990-1998; 2000; 2002; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 17)
  - Crime - Public Perception, 1992-1998; 2000 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 18)
  - Crime - Statistics, 1992-2000; 2002-2003; 2008 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 19)
  - Habeas - Loss of, 1991-1992; 1995-1997; 1999-2001; 2007; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 20)
  - Innocence - Exoneration After Execution, 1999-2001; 2004-2005 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 21)
  - Innocence - Life After Death Row, 1998-2004 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 22)
  - Innocence - Non-DNA, 1998-2004 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 23)
  - Innocence - Overviews, 1993-1994; 1997-2001; 2005-2007 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 24)
  - Innocence - Protection Act, 1999-2002; 2004-2005 (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 25)
  - Juveniles - Pre 2000 (1 of 2), 1994-1996; 1998; 2007; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 26)
  - Juveniles - Pre 2000 (2 of 2), 1992; 1995-1999; Undated (Box 1 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 27)
  - Juveniles, 2000 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 1)
  - Juveniles, 2001 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 2)
  - Juveniles, 2002 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 3)
  - Juveniles - 2002-2003, 2002-2004 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 4)
  - Juveniles - 2004, Simmons (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 5)
  - Juveniles, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 6)
  - Kendall, George Speeches, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 7)
  - Mentally Ill, 1998-2007 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 8)
  - Mentally Retarded - Pre 2000, 1991; 1993; 1997-1999 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 9)
  - Mentally Retarded - 2000, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 10)
  - Mentally Retarded - 2001, Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 11)
  - Mental Retardation - 2000, 2002, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 12)
  - Mental Retardation - 2004, 2004-2005; 2007 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 13)
  - Mental Retardation - Atkins Response, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 14)
  - Mental Retardation - HRW Report 2001 (1 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 15)
  - Mental Retardation - HRW Report 2001 (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 16)
  - Mental Retardation - Legislation, 2001 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 17)
  - Non-Death, Chicago Tribune, October, 2004 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 18)
  - Opinion - Anti-Death Penalty: Growing Public Opinion, 2002-2006 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 19)
  - Opinion - Anti-Death Penalty, 2008 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 20)
  - Opinion - Conservative Opposition, 2000-2001; 2003-2005; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 21)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-Pre 2000, 1977; 1982; 1990-2000; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 22)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-Pre 2001, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 23)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2000-2001 (1 of 2), Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 24)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2000-2001 (2 of 2) (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 25)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2004-2005, 2002-2005; 2007; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 26)
  - Opinion - Editorials, Anti-2005-2007 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 27)
  - Opinion - International, 1999-2000, 1996-2000; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 28)
  - Opinion - International, 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 29)
  - Opinion - International, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 30)
  - Opinion - International, 2004, 2001-2004 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 31)
  - Opinion - Pro, 1977; 1999-2002; 2004; 2006; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 32)
  - Opinion - Public, Through 2000, 1992; 1995; 1997-2000; 2004; Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 33)
  - Opinion - Public, 2001-2002, Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 34)
  - Opinion - Public, 2003-2004, Undated (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 35)
  - Opinion - Public, 2005-2006, 2001; 2005-2007 (Box 2 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 36)
  - Politicians, 1993; 1995; 1999-2005; Undated (Box 3 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 1)
  - Prison Conditions California (1 of 2), 1991; 1994-2001; 2004-2006; Undated (Box 3 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 2)
  - Prison Conditions California (2 of 2), 1985; 1987; 1991-1995; 1997-1999; Undated (Box 3 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 3)
  - Profiles, 1995; 1998-200; Undated (Box 3 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 4)
  - Prosecution Misconduct, 1992-1994; 1997-2005; 2007; Undated (Box 3 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 5)
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Chicago Tribune, Pre 2000, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 6)
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Chicago Tribune, 2000-2001; 2003; 2005; Undated (Box 3 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 7)
  - Prosecution Misconduct - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, 1999 (Box 4 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 1)
  - Prosecution Politics, 1999-2003 (Box 4 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 2)
  - Race - Death Penalty Articles (1 of 2), 1991; 1994-2004; Undated (Box 4 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 3)
  - Race - Death Penalty Articles (2 of 2), 1992-1994; 1996-1997; 1999-2001; 2003; Undated (Box 4 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 4)
  - Race - General, 1997-2004; 2007; Undated (Box 4 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 5)
  - Race - Official Studies and Law Reviews, 1986-1987; 1991; 1995-1998 (Box 4 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 6)
  - Race - Prisons, 1991-1994; 1997-1998; 2000; 2005; Undated (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 1)
  - Religion - Catholics, 1992; 1996-2000; 2004 (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 2)
  - Religion - Catholics, 2000-2007; Undated (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 3)
  - Religious Views - General, 2000-2004; 2007; Undated (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 4)
  - Religion - Jews, 1996-1997; 1999-2002; 2007-2009; Undated (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 5)
  - Resource Centers, 1996 (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 6)
  - Statistics Through 2001, 1990-2001; Undated (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 7)
  - Statistics Through 2007, 2002-2007 (Box 5 (2-Issues and Topics), Folder 8)